Susan Caperna Lloyd collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 7: Holy Week religious ritual
  - Subseries 1: General
    - Portfolio 13: Santos: Folk Icons of the Americas and the Philippines, 1978-2015, Depictions of Catholic saints in churches, processions, home altars, streets, graveyards, on walls or even in junkyards are everywhere across the Spanish conquest in the Americas and the Philippines. Originally ma
      - Print 3: A Filipino church santero cleans statues. An angel carries a chalice to catch the blood of Christ as another saint, eventually donned with a wig, looks on. Malolos, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987, AFC 2018/064: PH0862
      - Print 4: Lucy Reyes is a folk healer and devotee to Santo Niño, the Christ child brought to the Philippines by Magellan. She prays to him and other santos to gain power to heal. Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987, AFC 2018/064: PH0867
      - Print 5: Santos depicting Christ and the Apostles are carved by non-professionals, reflect Indian features, and are dressed in indigenous clothing. Santiago Atitlán church, Guatemala, 1989, AFC 2018/064: PH0865
      - Print 6: Street scene as vendors gather around a santo and a woman takes donations. Quito, Ecuador, 1978, AFC 2018/064: SL-03-02
      - Print 7: Santos depicting San Luis Obispo and the Virgin Mary. Beads of Indian women adorn the Virgin and San Luis wears an indigenous hat. Santuario de San Luis, Otavalo, Ecuador, 1978, AFC 2018/064: SL-03-01
      - Print 8: The Virgin Mary and Christ child in Mayan costume, sitting in shell-like niche. The Virgin is dark-skinned, reflecting the faces of the indigenous santos carvers. Santiago Atitlán church, Guatemala, 1989, AFC 2018/064: PH0864
      - Print 9: Santo of the Virgin Mary in the style of New Mexican santero carvers. Trampas church, New Mexico, 1980, AFC 2018/064: SL-09-01
      - Print 10: Men, women and children carry santos of the Christ child to the church for presentation. Feast of the Candelaria, Tepoztlán, Mexico, 1991, AFC 2018/064: SL-12-01
      - Print 11: Men, women and children carry santos of the Christ child to the church for presentation. Feast of the Candelaria, Tepoztlán, Mexico, 1991, AFC 2018/064: SL-12-01
      - Print 12: Procession of baby Christ santos carried to church on the Feast of the Candelaria, Tepoztlán, Mexico, 1991, AFC 2018/064: SL-12-01
      - Print 13: Kept at home and dressed in white clothing, a boy brings his santo of the Christ child to the church for presentation on the Candelaria feast day (February 2). Tepoztlán, Mexico, 1991, AFC 2018/064: SL-12-01
      - Print 14: Townspeople accompany a large santo of Christ through the streets, depicting his entry into Jerusalem prior to his Passion and death. Malolos, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987, AFC 2018/064: PH0866
      - Print 15: Villagers crowd a church to wash and oil a Christ santo, preparing it for the Passion story enactments during Holy Week. Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987, AFC 2018/064: PH0863
      - Print 16: The Nazareno, depicting Christ crowned with thorns, is a symbol of the Roman soldier's derision and abuse and displayed prominently in a church. Mulege Mission church, Mexico, 1978, AFC 2018/064: SL-02-01
      - Print 17: Christ Nazareno with crown of thorns. Mexico, 1991, AFC 2018/064: PH0860
      - Print 18: Santos of Christ Nazareno, the Sorrowing Virgin, and Christ Crucified. San Fernando Cathedral, Guaymas, Mexico, 1979, AFC 2018/064: SL-07-06
      - Print 19: A Christ santo carried in procession. Although Christ traditionally carried his own cross, the Tarahumara Indians take on this role during Holy Week rituals. Norogachi, Chihuahua, Mexico, 2001, AFC 2018/064: PH0870
      - Print 20: Ex-voto amulets dangling from a nailed hand of a Christ Crucified santo hangs in the San Xavier Mission church, Tucson, Arizona, 1978, AFC 2018/064: SL-01-03
      - Print 21: During Holy Week, children imitate the town processions by playing at being the crucified Christ. Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, 1989, AFC 2018/064: PH0861
      - Print 22: Christ Crucified. Mazatlán Cathedral, Mexico., 1979, AFC 2018/064: SL-07-01
      - Print 23: Painted santo of Christ with sampaguita flowers as village boys light candles in background. Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987, AFC 2018/064: PH0872
      - Print 24: A carved santo of the Crucifixion in the rough, elongated style of New Mexico santero carvers. It has been erected in a junkyard along a highway. Taos, New Mexico, 2013, AFC 2018/064: PH0868
      - Print 25: Detail of Christ's feet on the cross with geometric wall design. San Xavier Mission church, Tucson, Arizona, 1978, AFC 2018/064: SL-01-02
      - Print 26: Crucifix with missing Christ figure, Italy, 1983, AFC 2018/064: SL-10-02
      - Print 27: Crucifix with Christ figure in storage. Cuzco, Peru church, 1977, AFC 2018/064: SL-05-01
      - Print 28: Photo of child left in San Xavier Mission, Tucson, Arizona, 1978, AFC 2018/064: SL-01-02
      - Print 29: Photographs of the deceased left at the feet of a church santo, 1983, AFC 2018/064: SL-10-01
      - Print 30: Woman, wearing a cross, Mexico, 1978, AFC 2018/064: SL-02-02
      - Print 31: Immaculate Virgin in native textile cloak and basket. Mission church interior under renovation. Mazatlán, Mexico, 1979, AFC 2018/064: SL-07-04
      - Print 32: A man holds his Christ Child, a santo dressed in native clothing with pinned portrait of Our Lady of Guadalupe, Feast of the Candelaria, Tepoztlán, Mexico, 1991, AFC 2018/064: SL-12-01
      - Print 33: Boy assistant to a santero. Mission church, Guaymas, Mexico, 1979, AFC 2018/064: SL-06-01
      - Print 34: Child plays at being Christ in empty church as procession ensues outside. Monte Casino, Italy, 1983, AFC 2018/064: SL-10-05
    - Reviews (film, book, photography), 1979-1992, 1 folder (Box/folder 27/2)
    - Film festivals and photography exhibits, 1979-2009, 1 folder (Box/folder 27/3)
    - Queries and correspondence to magazines and journals, 1982-2008, 1 folder (Box/folder 27/4)
    - [Newspaper articles relating to Susan Lloyd's work on Holy Week religious ritual], 1982-2018, Includes the following articles: Ted Taylor, Ashlander's Work Examines Mystique of Easter Week Rituals, The Daily Tidings, February 28, 1989, page 7; Mary Ann Campbell, Couple View Filipino's Easter Crucifixion, The Mail Tribune, May 13, 1987, page 1B; Susan Lloyd, Remembering Manila, Lithiagraph, October 1987, pages 6-7; Carol Field, Sicily's Convergence of Ancient Beliefs, Review, May 10, 1992, pages 5, 9; JoNel Aleccia, The Meaning of Mothering, Mail Tribune, May 10, 1992, page 1C, 3C; David Barlett, Lloyd's photographic display shows realities in life, The Torch, February 15, 1982, page 9; Trio Plans to Film Sicilian Good Friday Ritual, The Daily Tidings, April 18, 1987, page 3; Laurie T. Conrad, One Woman's Rediscovery is a Passage into Antiquity, The Courier Times, April 9, 1992, page 12B, 9B; Susan Lloyd, Filipino People Face Decisions May 11, The Mail Tribune, May 8, 1987, page 17A; Author's Book Traces Roots, Rituals, The Daily Tidings, May 7, 1992, page 9; Photo Exhibit Focuses on the Spectacle of Rituals, Mail Tribune, March 1, 2002, page 9; Susan Lloyd, Holy Week in Sicily, Ashland Daily Tidings, April 24, 2004, page 7; Susan Lloyd, Notes of a Native Daughter, Siskiyou Journal, June/July 1987, page 4; Semana Santa En Chiantla, El Grafico, March 23, 1989, page 23; Terrie Claflin, Images of Holy Week, The Mail Tribune, March 19, 1989, pages 1C-2C; Spirited Sicily, San Francisco Examiner, April 24, 1988, pages T1-T10; Fra Noi, Volume XXXI, April 1992; Sarah Lemon, Rituals of Belief, Mail Tribune, April 1, 2018, pages C1, C10; Susan Lloyd, Religion, bloodshed both part of life in the Philippines, The Sunday Oregonian, April 19, 1987, page B4; Susan Lloyd, Following the Faithful, Albuquerque Journal Magazine, April 14, 1987, pages 4-7; Gail Caperna, An Interview with Susan Lloyd, Guide to the Arts, March 1992, pages 16-17.; 1 folder (Box 42)
    - Notes from lectures on Holy Week folk life project, 1983-1990, 1 folder (Box/folder 27/5)
    - Portfolio 16: Holy Week Folk Rituals, 1983-2013
      - Print version, 1983-2013, Every year at Easter time, the commemoration of the Passion, death, and Resurrection of Christ is celebrated across Hispanidad -- the countries of the Spanish colonization in the sixteenth century. The friars brought these rites to their colonies where the new religion, Catholicism, synthesized with preexisting rituals that had been taking place in the locations for millennia. In fact, the early Catholic Church fathers dated the first Easter to coincide with rituals to the pre-Christian deities, Attis and Cybele, then occurring in third century Rome. The Old World rituals seasonally celebrated the agricultural cycle where sacrifice to the gods were necessary to restore fertility and abundance in societies where the cultivation of wheat, corn, and rice was paramount. Although participants in contemporary Holy Week rituals dramatize the Passion, death, and Resurrection of Christ, sacrifices to the old gods are not entirely forgotten in the various communities but have been transferred to the "new" dying and resurrecting god, Christ. In examining the Old World fertility rituals, one becomes aware of several prescribed stages of ritual that can also be seen in contemporary Holy Week celebrations. They include: Fasting, Lamentation, Pilgrimage, Purification, Bloodletting, Casting Out Scapegoats, Combat and Struggle, and Death and Resurrection. Although tolerated, these rituals are often not sanctioned by the formal Catholic Church. Therefore, many contemporary Holy Week rituals across Hispania remain popular, folk rituals of the people. Susan Caperna Lloyd shot the photographs in this portfolio (and conducted research) at nine locations, some with repeat visits, from 1983-2013.; 1 portfolio (76 photographs): color Ultrachrome archival inkjet prints; 13 x 19 inch. (Box 58)
      - Digital version, 1983-2013, afc2018064_dc003; Digitized portfolio prints and caption document.; 76 still image files (jpg); 1 text file (txt)
      - Slide version, 1983-2013
        - Fasting, 1986-1998, AFC 2018/064: PH3777-PH3782; 6 color slides (35 mm); 3777, Costaleros in Seville, Spain are offered water as they fast under the one-ton platforms they carry during Holy Week, 1998; 3778, Ricky Martinez, Santa Fe, New Mexico, Fasting he holds a photo of his dead brother which he will carry with a cross to Chimayó, forty miles away, 1986; 3779, Antonio fasts in a hut during Holy Week before walking with a cross to sacred Mt. Arayat, San Fernando, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3780, Lucy Reyes, a Filipino healer, fasts in her bedroom before her crucifixion on Good Friday, Kapitangan, the Philippines, 1987; 3781, A young man who will carry his cross during Holy Week fasts in a secluded room before beginning his pilgrimage, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3782, Hooded penitents in Taxco, Mexico deny themselves sustenance before carrying their cactus crosses on Good Friday, 1991. (Box 19)
        - Lamentation, 1987-1989, 2001, AFC 2018/064: PH3783-PH3792; 10 color slides (35 mm); 3783, During Holy Week, Tarahumara drummers circle the church, lamenting the coming sacrifice on Good Friday, Norogachi, Chihuahua, Mexico, 2001; 3784, A healer, dressed as Christ, evokes tears as she attempts to heal a child during Holy Week, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3785, A woman playing the role of Mary, Christ's mother, cries as she learns that he will be crucified, Holy Thursday Passion Play, Marsala, Sicily, 1988; 3786, Playing the role of Mary Magdalene, a woman cries as Christ is led to his death, Holy Thursday Passion Play, Marsala, Sicily, 1988; 3787, The Virgin, La Macarena, is carried in procession on Good Friday in Seville, Spain, She has crystal tears on her cheeks, 1998; 3788, Mayan women chant a dirge, waiting for Maximón, a puppet representing half old god and new, to wake up, Holy Wednesday, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, 1989; 3789, Mayan woman at the dirge for Maximón, Holy Wednesday, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, 1989; 3790, Villagers cry as Lucy Reyes, a healer playing the role of Christ during Holy Week, passes by with her cross, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3791, Bullroarers in the streets during Holy Week make rattling, shrieking sounds to announce the coming sacrifice, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, 1989; 3792, Unknown. (Box 19)
        - Pilgrimage, 1986-1989, 2001, AFC 2018/064: PH3793-PH3800; 8 color slides (35 mm); 3793, During Holy Week, the Tarahumara walk to Norogachi where they wage mock battles between forces of good and evil, a pre-conquest folk tradition, Chihuahua, Mexico, 2001; 3794, Mayan villagers carry effigies of Christ during several Holy Week processions in Panajachél, Guatemala, 1989; 3795, A pilgrim's feet, he has walked for miles to the Chichicastenango church, Palm Sunday, Guatemala, 1989; 3796, A Santa Fe, New Mexico pilgrim walks with his cross during Holy Week to the Chimayó sanctuary forty miles away, 1986; 3797, Holy Week pilgrims on the road to Chimayó in the high country north of Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1986; 3798, Cross bearers walking on the freeway north of Santa Fe, New Mexico, head for the Chimayó sanctuary on Good Friday, 1986; 3799, A cross bearer dressed as Christ returns from his one hundred mile pilgrimage to Mt. Arayat, Holy Week, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3800, Pilgrims who have walked one hundred miles from Albuquerque, New Mexico, rest on Good Friday at the Chimayó sanctuary, New Mexico, 1987. (Box 19)
        - Purification, 1983-1991, AFC 2018/064: PH3801-PH3813; 13 color slides (35 mm); 3801, The church in Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, is purified with candles and incense on Good Friday, 1989; 3802, Elizabetta, outside her family's apartment, dresses in the chaste clothing of the Madonna, a role she plays on Good Friday, Trapani, Sicily, 1988; 3803, Elizabetta practices her role as the Madonna in the Good Friday procession, she waits in her family's courtyard in Trapani, Sicily, 1988; 3804, Villagers in Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala beautify the town with wreaths during Holy Week, 1989; 3805, Children in Seville, Spain join the Holy Week processions dressed in the white clothing of priests and nuns, 1998; 3806, Maximón, the Mayan puppet god feted during Holy Week, is purified by cleansing him with air deodorizer, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, 1989; 3807, Mayans use incense burners, carrying on a folk tradition of their ancestors, to purify their arrival on Palm Sunday at the Chichicastenango church, Guatemala, 1989; 3808, Taxco, Mexico flagellantes are cleansed before carrying their cactus crosses on Good Friday, 1991; 3809, Hooded members of the Confraternity of St. Michael purify themselves by wearing hoods and remaining nameless, Good Friday, Trapani, Sicily, 1983; 3810, A Taxco, Mexico flagellant wears a hood, remaining nameless and in meditation while carrying his cactus cross on Good Friday, 1991; 3811, Lucy Reyes reveals purity after stripped of her garments before undergoing crucifixion on Good Friday, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3812, A hooded confraternity assembles in the streets, hiding their identities as a symbol of purification, Good Friday, Trapani, Sicily, 1983; 3813, A statue of Christ is purified with oil in the local church on Holy Thursday, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987. (Box 19)
        - Bloodletting, 1987-1998, AFC 2018/064: PH3814-PH3824; 11 color slides (35 mm); 3814, Statue of Christ crucified, carved by folk santeros (saint carvers), Malolos church, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3815, Whips used for flagellation are soaked in oil during a "taktak" ceremony on Good Friday morning, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3816, "Taktak" whips are consecrated by a Filipino healer on Good Friday morning, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3817, A flagelate prostrates himself before a Station of the Cross on Good Friday, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3818, A flagelante, carrying a cross on Good Friday, is assisted by an actor portraying a Roman soldier, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3819, A flagelante kneels in the streets as girls dressed in white look on, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3820, Painted blood signifies the stigmata of saints and Christ's bloodshed, Marsala, Sicily, Holy Thursday Passion Play, 1998; 3821, Dripping red candle wax is intentional, giving the impression of blood, Good Friday procession, Seville, Spain, 1998; 3822, Real blood, through flagellation, on the back of a cactus bearer, Good Friday, Taxco, Mexico, 1991; 3823, Filipino healer Lucy Reyes is painted with the wounds of Christ, Holy Week, Kapitangan, the Philippines, 1987; 3824, An actor playing the role of Christ wears a mask painted to look like blood, Holy Thursday Passion Play, Marsala, Sicily, 1988. (Box 19)
        - Scapegoat, 1987-1989, 1999-2001, AFC 2018/064: PH3825-PH3830; 6 color slides (35 mm); 3825, An actor plays Christ, a scapegoat who dies to expiate communal sin, Marsala, Sicily Passion Play, 1988; 3826, The Yaqui of Pascua Village burn the scapegoat, Judas, who betrayed Christ, Good Friday, Tucson, Arizona, 1999; 3827, The Tarahumara burn a Judas figure symbolizing the Ladino landowner who expropriates Indian lands, Norogachi, Chihuahua, Mexico, 2001; 3828, A man is hung on a cross in the role of scapegoat, Christ, Good Friday, Kapitangan, the Philippines, 1987; 3829, A woman plays the role of Mary Magdalene -- in Bible accounts, a sinner and scapegoat cast out of the community, Marsala, Sicily Passion Play, 1988; 3830, Maximón, the Mayan puppet deity, is paraded through the streets on Holy Thursday, as a scapegoat he (in part) represents the traitor, Pedro de Alvarado (Spanish conqueror), Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, 1989. (Box 19)
        - Combat and struggle, 1987-1991, 1998-2001, AFC 2018/064: PH3829-PH3839; 9 color slides (35 mm); 3831, Christ falls under his cross while Mary fends off the Roman soldiers, Marsala, Sicily Passion Play, 1988; 3832, Villagers play the role of Roman soldiers on Good Friday, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3833, Lucy Reyes, a village healer playing the role of Christ, is pushed to her crucifixion by actors playing Roman soldiers, Good Friday, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3834, Tarahumara children participate in the folk dances between forces of good and evil on Good Friday, Norogachi, Chihuahua, Mexico, 2001; 3835, Portatori struggle with their one-ton ceto depicting Christ falling under his cross, Good Friday, Trapani, Sicily, 1988; 3836, A flagelante carries his cactus cross and withstands the candle flame which will eventually burn his hand, Good Friday, Taxco, Mexico, 1991; 3837, The Guardia Civil keeps the crowd back as the carriers of the Virgin take a break, Good Friday, Seville, Spain, 1998; 3838, Children carry their homemade ceto in imitation of their elders, Procession of Mysteries, Good Friday, Trapani, Sicily, 1988; 3839, Carriers of the Ceto del Popolo struggle under the one-ton platform holding statues (misteri) depicting the Stations of the Cross, Procession of Mysteries, Good Friday, Trapani, Sicily, 1988. (Box 19)
        - Death and resurrection, 1987-1989, 2001-2005, AFC 2018/064: PH3840-PH3845; 5 color slides (35 mm); 3840, Lucy Reyes, a village healer, is nailed to a cross on Good Friday, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3841, Nails fully penetrate the hands and feet of Lucy Reyes, a village healer, but there are no signs of blood, Good Friday, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3842, A village healer, Lucy Reyes, hangs on a cross for three hours on Good Friday, she is crucified yearly to gain power to heal, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987; 3843, The Yaqui dress the Christ statue in a feminine skirt, a folk custom symbolizing fertility, after his Good Friday crucifixion, Hermosillo, Mexico, 2002; 3844, Called the empalao, young men wear embroideries made by their mothers as they are strapped to wooden beams representing Christ carrying his cross, Good Friday, Valverde de la Vera, Spain, 2005; 3845, After Christ's death, Tarahumara women carry the Virgin to "reunite" with him at his resurrection, Norogachi, Chihuahua, Mexico, 2001. (Box 19)
        - Death and resurrection, 1987-1989, 2001-2005, AFC 2018/064: PH3846-PH3852; 8 color slides (35 mm); 3846, Mayan men dance with a statue of the Virgin, symbolizing fertility and the conjunction of male and female, Holy Saturday, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, 1989; 3847, Yaqui Fariseos (enemies of Christ) are converted by flowers, Holy Saturday, Hermosillo, Mexico, 2002; 3848, Townsmen sit in front of bread decorations, folk symbols of agriculture and fertility that the village women have made, Easter Sunday, San Biago Platani, Sicily, 1988; 3849, Members of the CofraDía de San Juan wear newly embroidered clothing the village women have made, Easter Sunday, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, 1989; 3850, A family in Trapani, Sicily reunites on Easter Sunday, 1988; 3851, Mayan women bring flowers to the church on Easter Sunday, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, 1989; 3852, After removal of crucifixion nails, the feet of healer, Lucy Reyes, are bloodless, contrasting with other local Good Friday rites of male bloodletting, Kapitangan, Bulacan, the Philippines, 1987. (Box 20)
        - [Slide logs AFC 2018/064: PH0873-PH3852], 1 folder (Box/folder 38/13)
    - [Holy Week rituals], 1983-2017, Manuscripts and ephemera related to Holy Week folk rituals.; 1 folder (Box/folder 27/6)
    - Ephemera collected at locations where Easter time folk rituals of Holy Week are held (1 of 4), 1983-2018, Includes brochures, flyers, booklets, postcards, pamphlets, posters, maps, news articles, liturgical devotions, programs, and calendars. Locations include Trapani, Sicily, Seville, Spain, Antigua, Guatemala, Valverde de la Vera, Spain, Durango and Bilbao, Spain, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, Malolos, Bulacan, the Philippines, San Juan Pueblo, New Mexico, Salamanca, Spain.; 1 folder (Box/folder 27/7)
    - Ephemera collected at locations where Easter time folk rituals of Holy Week are held (2 of 4), 1983-2018, Includes brochures, flyers, booklets, postcards, pamphlets, posters, maps, news articles, liturgical devotions, programs, and calendars. Locations include Trapani, Sicily, Seville, Spain, Antigua, Guatemala, Valverde de la Vera, Spain, Durango and Bilbao, Spain, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, Malolos, Bulacan, the Philippines, San Juan Pueblo, New Mexico, Salamanca, Spain.; 1 folder (Box/folder 27/8)
    - Ephemera collected at locations where Easter time folk rituals of Holy Week are held (3 of 4), 1983-2018, Includes brochures, flyers, booklets, postcards, pamphlets, posters, maps, news articles, liturgical devotions, programs, and calendars. Locations include Trapani, Sicily, Seville, Spain, Antigua, Guatemala, Valverde de la Vera, Spain, Durango and Bilbao, Spain, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, Malolos, Bulacan, the Philippines, San Juan Pueblo, New Mexico, Salamanca, Spain.; 1 folder (Box/folder 27/9)
    - Ephemera collected at locations where Easter time folk rituals of Holy Week are held (4 of 4), 1983-2018, Includes brochures, flyers, booklets, postcards, pamphlets, posters, maps, news articles, liturgical devotions, programs, and calendars. Locations include Trapani, Sicily, Seville, Spain, Antigua, Guatemala, Valverde de la Vera, Spain, Durango and Bilbao, Spain, Santiago Atitlán, Guatemala, Malolos, Bulacan, the Philippines, San Juan Pueblo, New Mexico, Salamanca, Spain.; 1 folder (Box/folder 39/1)